<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Usability on VMware Tanzu - Developer Advocates</title>
    <link>https://www.makejarnotwar.com/tags/usability/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Usability on VMware Tanzu - Developer Advocates</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.makejarnotwar.com/tags/usability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nate Schutta</title>
      <link>https://www.makejarnotwar.com/advocate/nate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.makejarnotwar.com/advocate/nate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nathaniel T. Schutta is a software architect focused on cloud computing and building usable applications. A proponent of polyglot programming, Nate has written multiple books and appeared in &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ntschutta.io/#publications&#34;&gt;various videos&lt;/a&gt;. Nate is a seasoned speaker regularly presenting at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ntschutta.io/#talks&#34;&gt;conferences worldwide&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://nofluffjuststuff.com/home/main&#34;&gt;No Fluff Just Stuff symposia&lt;/a&gt;, meetups, universities, and user groups. In addition to his day job, Nate is an adjunct professor at the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.umsec.umn.edu&#34;&gt;University of Minnesota&lt;/a&gt; where he teaches students to embrace (and evaluate) technical change. Driven to rid the world of bad presentations, Nate coauthored the book &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.safaribooksonline.com/library/view/presentation-patterns/9781491954980/&#34;&gt;Presentation Patterns&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href=&#34;http://nealford.com&#34;&gt;Neal Ford&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://matthewjmccullough.com&#34;&gt;Matthew McCullough&lt;/a&gt;. Nate recently published &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.safaribooksonline.com/library/view/thinking-architecturally/9781492034421/&#34;&gt;Thinking Architecturally&lt;/a&gt; available as a free download from &lt;a href=&#34;https://tanzu.vmware.com/content/ebooks/thinking-architecturally&#34;&gt;VMware&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nate&amp;rsquo;s presentations cover a variety of topics ranging from architecture fundamentals, mobile design, usability, cloud computing, JavaScript and everything in between. His current slate of talks can be found in &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ntschutta.io/#abstracts&#34;&gt;Talk Abstracts&lt;/a&gt; however additional presentations can also be found at his &lt;a href=&#34;https://nofluffjuststuff.com/conference/speaker/nathaniel_schutta&#34;&gt;NFJS Speaker Page&lt;/a&gt;. If you are interested in having Nate speak at your event, please &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:nschutta@vmware.com&#34;&gt;reach out&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>