<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spring on VMware Tanzu - Developer Advocates</title>
    <link>https://www.makejarnotwar.com/tags/spring/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Spring on VMware Tanzu - Developer Advocates</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.makejarnotwar.com/tags/spring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bob Brindley</title>
      <link>https://www.makejarnotwar.com/advocate/bob/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.makejarnotwar.com/advocate/bob/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bob Brindley travels the world spreading the good word according to Tanzu and Spring to any and all that will hear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He has been a developer advocate for 5 years and still smells terrific.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cora Iberkleid</title>
      <link>https://www.makejarnotwar.com/advocate/cora/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.makejarnotwar.com/advocate/cora/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cora Iberkleid is an Advisory Cloud Application and Platform Architect at VMware, where she helps enterprises leverage modern technologies like Spring Boot, Spring Cloud, and Cloud Foundry in order to deliver better quality software faster. Prior to joining VMware, she spent nearly a decade designing and building enterprise integration applications as part of the Professional Services organizations at Sun Microsystems and Oracle. She has previously spoken at SpringOne Platform, SpringOne Tour, SpringConnect, deliver:Agile, Cloud Native New York and New York City Spring User Group.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jakub Pilimon</title>
      <link>https://www.makejarnotwar.com/advocate/jakub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.makejarnotwar.com/advocate/jakub/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/JakubPilimon&#34;&gt;Jakub&lt;/a&gt; is a Developer Advocate at &lt;a href=&#34;https://vmware.com&#34;&gt;VMware&lt;/a&gt;, blogger, programmer, and trainer. He loves to tackle complex enterprises with Domain-Driven Design, Test-Driven Development and Spring. Architecture is a main area of interest, too. When he doesn&amp;rsquo;t program, he rides motorbikes, skis or practices kitesurfing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He writes a &lt;a href=&#34;https://pillopl.github.io&#34;&gt;DZone MVB awarded blog&lt;/a&gt; and his pet projects can be found at &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ddd-by-examples&#34;&gt;https://github.com/ddd-by-examples&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Josh Long</title>
      <link>https://www.makejarnotwar.com/advocate/joshlong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.makejarnotwar.com/advocate/joshlong/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Josh (&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/starbuxman&#34;&gt;@starbuxman&lt;/a&gt;) has (officially) been a Spring Developer Advocate since 2010. Josh is a Java Champion, author of 6 books (including O’Reilly’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/Cloud-Native-Java-Designing-Resilient/dp/1449374646, Spring Cloud, and Cloud Foundry&#34;&gt;Cloud Native Java: Designing Resilient Systems with Spring Boot&lt;/a&gt; and the upcoming &lt;a href=&#34;http://reactivespring.io/&#34;&gt;Reactive Spring&lt;/a&gt;) and numerous best-selling video trainings (including &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.safaribooksonline.com/library/view/building-microservices-with/9780134192468/&#34;&gt;Building Microservices with Spring Boot Livelessons&lt;/a&gt; with Spring Boot co-founder Phil Webb), and an open-source contributor (Spring Boot, Spring Integration, Spring Cloud, Activiti and Vaadin), &lt;a href=&#34;http://bit.ly/a-bootiful-podcast&#34;&gt;a podcaster (A Bootiful Podcast)&lt;/a&gt; and a &lt;a href=&#34;http://bit.ly/spring-tips-playlist&#34;&gt;screencaster&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mario Gray</title>
      <link>https://www.makejarnotwar.com/advocate/mario/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.makejarnotwar.com/advocate/mario/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mr. Gray is a Principal Technologist at VMWare with over 20 years of experience in software development, software architecture. He is co-author of Apress’s Pro Spring Integration. He’s helped organizations large and small build service-based architectures in a number of different runtimes and platforms over the decades, but adopting Spring in 2004, and using it whenever possible since, was a no-brainer that culminated in joining the Spring team in 2017. As a Spring Developer Advocate, Mario loves to engage and inspire developers and businesses in the Pivotal ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Heckler</title>
      <link>https://www.makejarnotwar.com/advocate/mheckler/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.makejarnotwar.com/advocate/mheckler/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://thehecklers.com/&#34;&gt;Mark Heckler&lt;/a&gt; is a software developer &amp;amp; Spring Developer Advocate at VMware, conference speaker, published author, &amp;amp; Java Champion focusing upon developing innovative production-ready software at velocity for the cloud. His latest book, link:&lt;a href=&#34;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/spring-boot-up/9781492076971/[Spring&#34;&gt;https://learning.oreilly.com/library/view/spring-boot-up/9781492076971/[Spring&lt;/a&gt; Boot: Up &amp;amp; Running!], is available for early access &lt;em&gt;now&lt;/em&gt; and is scheduled for publication August 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an engineer and an MBA, Mark has worked with key players in the manufacturing, retail, medical, scientific, telecom, and financial industries and various public sector organizations to develop and deliver critical capabilities on time and on budget. He is a committed open source contributor and author/curator of a developer-focused &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.thehecklers.com&#34;&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt; and an occasionally interesting &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/mkheck&#34;&gt;Twitter account&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nate Schutta</title>
      <link>https://www.makejarnotwar.com/advocate/nate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.makejarnotwar.com/advocate/nate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nathaniel T. Schutta is a software architect focused on cloud computing and building usable applications. A proponent of polyglot programming, Nate has written multiple books and appeared in &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ntschutta.io/#publications&#34;&gt;various videos&lt;/a&gt;. Nate is a seasoned speaker regularly presenting at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ntschutta.io/#talks&#34;&gt;conferences worldwide&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://nofluffjuststuff.com/home/main&#34;&gt;No Fluff Just Stuff symposia&lt;/a&gt;, meetups, universities, and user groups. In addition to his day job, Nate is an adjunct professor at the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.umsec.umn.edu&#34;&gt;University of Minnesota&lt;/a&gt; where he teaches students to embrace (and evaluate) technical change. Driven to rid the world of bad presentations, Nate coauthored the book &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.safaribooksonline.com/library/view/presentation-patterns/9781491954980/&#34;&gt;Presentation Patterns&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href=&#34;http://nealford.com&#34;&gt;Neal Ford&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://matthewjmccullough.com&#34;&gt;Matthew McCullough&lt;/a&gt;. Nate recently published &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.safaribooksonline.com/library/view/thinking-architecturally/9781492034421/&#34;&gt;Thinking Architecturally&lt;/a&gt; available as a free download from &lt;a href=&#34;https://tanzu.vmware.com/content/ebooks/thinking-architecturally&#34;&gt;VMware&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nate&amp;rsquo;s presentations cover a variety of topics ranging from architecture fundamentals, mobile design, usability, cloud computing, JavaScript and everything in between. His current slate of talks can be found in &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ntschutta.io/#abstracts&#34;&gt;Talk Abstracts&lt;/a&gt; however additional presentations can also be found at his &lt;a href=&#34;https://nofluffjuststuff.com/conference/speaker/nathaniel_schutta&#34;&gt;NFJS Speaker Page&lt;/a&gt;. If you are interested in having Nate speak at your event, please &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:nschutta@vmware.com&#34;&gt;reach out&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>